https://www.velsoft.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Last modified: May 2018
This Privacy Policy applies to all of Velsoft’s products, services and websites.
We are committed to the privacy of your information. The security and confidentiality of your information is our highest priority. Your email address and other private information are never shared without your express permission.
If you choose to visit Velsoft’s websites, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the province of Nova Scotia, Canada.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact our Privacy Officer at
Privacy Officer
Email: privacy@velsoft.com
185 Provost St.
New Glasgow, Nova Scotia, Canada
B2H 2P8
Information we collect and how we use it
In order to better service our customers and prospects, we may collect the following types of information:
Information you provide– When you sign up for a product download or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, organization, phone number and email address). When purchasing from us, your payment information, including credit card numbers, are user-input through our external, accredited online payment provider. That information is held securely by this entity and destroyed when no longer needed. We do not have direct access to your payment information.
Cookies– When you visit our sites, we may send cookies – small files containing a string of characters – to your computer or other device to uniquely identify your browser. We later use the cookies to improve the quality of service and tracking user trends.
User communications– When you send email or other communications to Velsoft, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We will use the information you provide to contact you regarding our products and services.
Choices for personal information
When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.
You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case we may not be able to provide those services to you. Velsoft only collects the minimum amount of information needed to complete a transaction.
The personal information we collect is retained only as long as it is needed to provide you the services you want. Information on customers is kept as long as they continue being customers with Velsoft. If you cease being a customer, we will keep you on our mailing lists to receive promotional material. If you ask, we will remove you from this list.
As an individual, you have the right to access any of your personal information that we store, and can request that we provide it to you in an easily accessible and portable format. You can also request that we revise any data found to be inaccurate, or delete data at your request (where permitted by law). Every information request will be processed without delay within 28 days of being received. Personal information and privacy inquiries can be forwarded to Velsoft’s Privacy Officer, or your Velsoft account representative.
Citizens of the European Union also have the right to object to the use of their data in a data processing function, given appropriate grounds, as outlined in the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). EU citizens may also ask that we restrict the use of their personal data in processing functions in particular circumstances.
Information sharing
Velsoft will never share your personal information with other companies or individuals without your express consent.
There are certain circumstances where we are required to release information to satisfy the following:  We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Velsoft, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
Please contact us at the address below for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.
Information security
We take appropriate security measures to protect against the unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.
We restrict the access of personal information to Velsoft employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.
Enforcement
Velsoft regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or our treatment of personal information by contacting our Privacy Officer at
Privacy Officer
Email: privacy@velsoft.com
185 Provost St.
New Glasgow, Nova Scotia, Canada
B2H 2P8
When we receive privacy complaints, it is our policy to contact the complainant regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Velsoft and an individual.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date.
If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, feel free to contact our Privacy Officer at
Privacy Officer
Email: privacy@velsoft.com
185 Provost St.
New Glasgow, Nova Scotia, Canada
B2H 2P8
COURSEWARE SAMPLE
Courseware you can customize.
Your privacy is important to us. For more information, take a look at
our Privacy Policy.
I agree to receiving electronic content
SUBMIT
x
Proceed to download
View an eLearning Course
Begin
Download a SCORM sample to try in your LMS
Download
View an eLearning Course
Your privacy is important to us. For more information, take a look at
our Privacy Policy.
I agree to receiving electronic content
SUBMIT
SCORM COMPLIANT
Available as an eLearning Course
Your privacy is important to us. For more information, take a look at
our Privacy Policy.
I agree to receiving electronic content
SUBMIT
x
ELEARNING SAMPLE
eLearning you can customize.
Your privacy is important to us. For more information, take a look at
our Privacy Policy.
I agree to receiving electronic content
SUBMIT
x
COURSEWARE SAMPLE
Courseware you can customize.
Your privacy is important to us. For more information, take a look at
our Privacy Policy.
I agree to receiving electronic content
SUBMIT
x
Safe & Inclusive Workplace
By Velsoft
Your privacy is important to us. For more information, take a look at
our Privacy Policy.
I agree to receiving electronic content
SUBMIT
x
Seeing Double
August Only
Your privacy is important to us. For more information, take a look at
our Privacy Policy.
I agree to receiving electronic content
SUBMIT
x
NAME
EMAIL
PHONE
YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO US. FOR MORE INFORMATION, TAKE A LOOK AT OUR
PRIVACY POLICY
.
I AGREE TO RECEIVING ELECTRONIC CONTENT
BEGIN JOURNEY
x
HOME
TRAINING PRODUCTS
Courseware
eLearning Courses
Virtual Campus
LOGIN
We use cookies to ensure that we deliver the best customer experience possible by optimizing our website performance, enabling live chat and social media features, and analyzing our web traffic with our analytics partners. If you click ‘Accept Cookies’ or continue using this site, you are agreeing to the use of cookies per our Privacy Policy.
Accept Cookies Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Always Enabled
Login
Username or email address *
Password *
Lost your password?
